Just where does she fit in this crazy world
Andie the Great is a comedy, drama, tv movie film directed by Josh Romyn.
After dropping out of University and moving back in with her parents, an amiable young woman  reconnects with her former
high school friends and spends time with her family—while she tries to figure out her place in the world.
Andie Offerman, played by Matreya Scarrwener.
Hans, played by Clive Holloway.
Dean Offerman, played by Michael Wener.
Karen Offerman, played by Dollie Scarr.
Neil Offerman, played by Ameko Eks Mass Carroll.
Penny, played by Jess McLeod.
Rosalie Anderson MacDowell (born April 21, 1958) is an
American actress and former fashion model.
MacDowell is known for her starring film roles in romantic comedies and dramas.
She has modeled for Calvin Klein and has been a
spokeswoman for L'Oréal since 1986.
Her early films include Greystoke: The Legend of Tarzan, Lord of
the Apes (1984) and the Brat Pack vehicle film St.
Elmo's Fire (1985).
Her breakout role was in Sex, Lies, and Videotape (1989) which earned her the Independent Spirit Award for Best
Female Lead and a nomination for a Golden Globe Award for Best Actress – Motion Picture Drama.
She then starred in a series of films including Green Card (1990), Groundhog Day (1993), Short Cuts (1993), Four Weddings
and a Funeral (1994), Unstrung Heroes (1995), Michael (1996), Multiplicity (1996), and The Muse (1999).
MacDowell played supporting film roles in Beauty Shop (2005), Footloose (2011), Magic Mike XXL (2015), The
Last Laugh (2019), Ready or Not (2019), The Other Zoey (2024) and Red Right Hand (2024).
She starred in a number of independent films, most notable Love After Love (2017) She co-starred opposite her daughter
Margaret Qualley in the Netflix miniseries Maid (2021) for which she was nominated for a Golden Globe Award.
In 2023, MacDowell began starring in the Hallmark
Channel fantasy drama series, The Way Home.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.